So friends, ICICI L brand has
disclosed its quarter 4 results.
Before that, let me tell you that the company has
announced a dividend which is
based on the seventh share.  Let's
see what the income
is first.  Which was Rs 6610 crore in the last quarter.
Last year it was Rs 5851 crore.  Now it has become Rs
crore.  If checked yearly, there
is an increase of about 18%.  If we look at the quarterly badge,
it is flat.  Then let us see
what the company's expenses turn out to be.
Which was Rs 639 crore in the last quarter.
Last year it was Rs 5435 crore.  Now it has become 672
crores.  Expenses are also fine.  It is under control.
Then let us check what the net profit
turns out to be.  Which was Rs 658 crore in the last quarter.
Last year it was 59 crores.  Now it has become
546 crores.  If we check the yearly wages,
there is an increase of 8%.  If we
check the quarterly wages, there
is a decline there.  But the reason behind the decline in this quarter
is provision.  The company has lost
₹39 crore as provisions in this quarter.
Due to this, a slight
dip in profit is being seen.
Overall, the result is fine.  It
is average.  Finally let us check what the EPS
comes out to be, which was 13.25 in the last quarter,
last year it was 10.29,
now it is 10.97.  I hope you
found the video inspiring, so please like and subscribe to this channel.  Thank
you.